prokabaddi.com 2018-10-12

# Pro Kabaddi - Privacy Policy | ProKabaddi.com

This website [www.probkabaddi.com](http://www.probkabaddi.com/) (“ **Website** ”) is maintained and operated by Mashal Sports Private Limited, having its registered office at2nd Floor, Esteem Regency, 6 Richmond Road, Bangalore 560025, Karnataka, India (“ **Mashal** ” and/or “ **We** ”). This PrivacyPolicy covers the information **We** collect from the user(s) (“ **User(s)** ” and/or “ **You** ”) of the Website and/orthe services on the Website. This Privacy Policy should be read in conjunction and together with the Terms of Use available at <https://www.prokabaddi.com/terms-conditions>.

Personal Information of a User is collected if the User registers with the Website, accesses the Website or takes any action on the Website or uses oraccesses the Services/ Subscription Services as defined in the Terms of Use.

Here are our privacy principles:

Providing information to us is your choice.

  * You can choose to have the Personal Information provided by You deleted.

  * You always have the ability to opt-out of receiving communications from us.

### Information Collection and Use

The Personal Information which You may provide to us and/or which we may collect is or could be the following:

  * Your registration details which may include the password provided by You. You may note that We adopt reasonable security measures to protect Yourpassword from being exposed or disclosed to any third parties other than Mashal.

  * Your shipping, billing, tax registration, and other information pertaining to Your transactions on the Website or in related to the Services.

  * Your usage behavior of the Website.

  * Details of the computer system or computer network which You use to visit the Website and undertake any activity on the Website.

Our primary purposes in collecting information from You are to allow You to use the Website and various features and Services on or in relation to theWebsite or any Properties; contact you for any services provided by Mashal or its affiliates or its various service providers or business partners andadvertisers; to record Your information and details as permitted and required under applicable laws, statutory direction or judiciary orders; to servevarious promotion materials and advertising materials to you; and such other uses as provided in the User Agreement and this Privacy Policy. We may alsouse the information for transactional emails or to provide You with information, direct marketing, online and offline advertising and other materialsregarding products, services and other offers from time to time in connection with the Wesbite or Mashal or its parent, subsidiary and affiliated companies(“ **Platform Entities** ”) and its joint ventures.

We may also collect information to track User behavior and preferences for internal analytics from all Users of the Website. This information is collectedthrough the use of server log files and tracking technologies to collect and analyze certain types of technical information and may include cookies and webbeacons.

We may combine your Personal Information, other information and information collected from tracking technologies and aggregate it with informationcollected from other Users using our Website to attempt to provide You with a better experience on our Website.

You understand, agree and acknowledge that our collection, storage and processing of your Personal Information is for a lawful purpose connected with afunction or activity of the Platform Entities and its joint ventures. You further understand, agree and acknowledge that your Personal Information which isclassified as sensitive personal information as per applicable laws is considered necessary for Mashal to provide various services on its Website to Youand for Your usage of the Website and other services provided by Mashal in relation to the Website.

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

Mashal is the recipient of all the Personal Information and shall exercise reasonable commercial endeavors for the prevention of the Personal Informationprovided by the Users. We may enable access of the Users’ information to the Platform Entities, joint ventures, agents or third parties for the purposes ofthe services provided by them or for any other marketing related activity undertaken by or on behalf of the Platform Entities and/or its joint ventures. Wewill ensure on reasonable commercial efforts basis that the third parties and agents employed by us for the purposes of the Website are under an obligationto maintain confidentiality with respect to the Personal Information provided by the Users and to use it strictly for the purposes of the Website only.

Mashal may disclose your Personal Information to such extent as Mashal may deem necessary for you to enter into commercial transactions with other users ofthe Website.

### Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement

Mashal cooperates with mandated government and law enforcement agencies or to any third parties by an order under law for the time being in force toenforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about You to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in oursole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process, to protect the property and rights of Mashal or a third party, toprotect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity. Mashal may also provide yourPersonal Information to various tax authorities upon any demand or request from them.

### Business Transfers

Mashal may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your Personal Information, in connection with a merger, acquisition,reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy. Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will ensure that the Personal Information You haveprovided through the Website is stored and used by the transferee in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.

### Email Policies

Mashal may use your Personal Information for the aforementioned purposes of the Website. You have full control regarding which of these emails You want toreceive. If You decide at any time that You no longer wish to receive such communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided inany of the communications. Please note that once we receive your request, it may take an additional period of time for your opt-out to become effective.

### Deleting Your Information

If You wish to have the Personal Information that You have provided to us deleted, You can always do so by sending a request to us on the e-mail id of ourCustomer Services department provided at the bottom of this page. You may note that deletion of certain Personal Information may lead to cancellation ofyour registration with the Website and your access to certain features of the Website.

### Security

Mashal uses ordinary industry standard technology designed to help keep your Personal Information safe. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts allinformation You put in before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access. To preventunauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure correct use of information, We will employ commercially reasonable and practicable securitypractices and procedures and security methods and technologies. We will also ensure on reasonable commercial efforts basis that any agent or third partythat we employ complies with the same security standards as us for the protection of your Personal Information.

Your information may be transferred to or be maintained on computers, computer systems and computer resources located outside of your state or countrywhere the privacy laws may not be as protective as those where you live. If You are located outside India and choose to provide information to us, pleasebe aware that Mashal keeps or transfers information to India and processes it there. Your submission of such information represents your agreement to thattransfer.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information over the Internet is not completely secure. Although We strive to protect your personal data, We cannotguarantee the security of your data while it is being transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once We have received yourinformation, We have commercially reasonable procedures and security features in place to reasonably endeavor to prevent unauthorized access.

### Links to Other Sites / Financial Data

We provide links to other websites for your convenience and information. These sites may have their own privacy policies in place, which we recommend Youreview if You visit any linked websites. We are not responsible for the content of linked sites or any use of the sites.

While transacting with other users of the Website, You may provide your financial information including without limitation your bank account details,credit card account details or your details pertaining to any payment settlement or pre-paid instrument service provider. You understand, agree andacknowledge that the Website and Mashal never receives Your financial and payment information from these service providers. Your personal information,sensitive personal information and financial information will be dealt by these service providers in accordance with their respective privacy policies andother terms and conditions and Mashal and Website shall not be liable, accountable or responsible for your personal information, sensitive personalinformation and financial information which you provide to these service providers.

### Changes in Privacy Policy

From time to time We may update this Privacy Policy. Your continued subscription to our Services constitutes an acceptance of the then-current PrivacyPolicy and Terms of Use so We encourage You to visit this page periodically to review any changes.

### Phishing

Identity theft and the practice currently known as "phishing" are of great concern to Mashal. Safeguarding information to help protect You from identitytheft is a top priority. We do not and will not, at any time, request your credit card information or national identification numbers in a non-secure orunsolicited e-mail or telephone communication.

### Contact Us

If You have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of Mashal or your dealings with the Website, You can contact us via the links at thebottom of the page.

### Grievances

If you have any questions or grievance or want to delete or modify your Personal Information, you shall mark your correspondence as “Grievance/Complaint”(given under the heading “Contact Us”) to hello@prokabaddi.com. Any communication which is not marked as such shall not be treated as a valid and bindingcommunication for the purpose of this Privacy Policy and applicable laws with respect to this Privacy Policy.
